Curriculum Vitae

Bosaso, Puntland - Somalia Telephone: +252 90 7728369 Email: <u>Hayaangroup93@gmail.com</u>

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name: Mohamed Ali Ahmed

Date of Birth: Jan 1th, 1999

Place of Birth: Laasqorey, Puntland Somalia

Nationality: Somalia

Profession: Computer science

I am passionate about Information Technology and the Organization. My three years of study and my practical field work experience have strongly confirmed Computer science as the career choice for me. I am now looking forward to a career focused on my passion for the Computer, presenting opportunities to work with similar minded people.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Mathematics
- Computer Science especially programmer such as Web Development
- Good interpersonal skills and ability to establish and maintain effective working relations in a multi-cultural team with sensitive and respect for diversity.
- Android Mobile removal defect
- Good computer skills including Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, Power point, Outlook and so on
- Database management

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

September 2020 – May 2022 Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Bosaso - Somalia

September 2019 _ May 2020 Diploma of Computer Science

CityCot Collage _ Somalia

October 2022 _ December 2022 Certificate of Web development

University of Bosaso - Somalia

April 2022 _ May 2022 Certificate of Word press

University of Bosaso - Somalia

August 2015 – June 2019 Certificate of High School

Al-Furqaan High School

August 2015 – June 2018 Certificate of Sharia Institute

Iqra Sharia Institute

WORK EXPERIENCE

- > Mathematics Teacher in Al-Haramain school Bosaso Somalia one year (2021-2022)
- ▶ Islamic Teacher Darul-Birri in Badhan Somalia One year (2018-2019)
- Home Teacher in Badhan Somalia Two year (2017-2019)
- Database Manager in Tayasan pharmacy Bosaso Somalia one year (2020-2021)
- Transitional Puntland Electoral Commission(TPEC) Operator, Voter's information Registration (01/01/2023 20/01/2023)

REFERENCES

1. Name: Mr. Mohamud Ahmed Yusuf

Tel: +252 907 729592

Email: msheikh@gmail.com

Job title: Manager Al-Haramain School Bosaso

2. Name: Mr. Muse Ali Shaaciye

Tel: +252 907 734649

Email: Shaaciye26@gmail.com

Job title: Manager Tayasan branch Bosaso

3. Name: Mr. Mohamud Abdi Siyaad

Tel: +252 907 756582

Email: maxamuudcabdi623@gmail.com

Job title: Manager Sahan Spare Parts

4. Name: Mr. Abdihakiin Mohamed Warsame

Tel: +252 907 779774

Email: Suudi9774@gmail.com

Job title: Manager Amal School Bosaso